[{"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "120611pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "RB", ",", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 32, "question": "Jesse, how are you?", "question_tokens": ["Jesse", ",", "how", "are", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 33, "answer": "I'm doing well, Piers.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'m", "doing", "well", ",", "Piers", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120611pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 34, "question": "How re you?", "question_tokens": ["How", "re", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "NN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 35, "answer": "You are looking very well.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "are", "looking", "very", "well", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120611pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "IN", "POS", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 90, "question": "Is that right?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "that", "right", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 91, "answer": "Yes, that's true.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "that", "'s", "true", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120611pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "."], "qSentId": 114, "question": "How does that work?", "question_tokens": ["How", "does", "that", "work", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 115, "answer": "I will.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "will", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "120611pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "NNS", ",", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 135, "question": "You're basically endorsing a form of fascism, aren't you?", "question_tokens": ["You", "'re", "basically", "endorsing", "a", "form", "of", "fascism", ",", "are", "n't", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", ",", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 136, "answer": "We're already fascists, Piers.", "answer_tokens": ["We", "'re", "already", "fascists", ",", "Piers", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120611pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", ":", "RB", "VBZ", "WP", "PRP", "VBD", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 151, "question": "Why is it just one way?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "is", "it", "just", "one", "way", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "PRP", "RB", "CD", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 152, "answer": "Well, I guess that -- here's what I thought when I read your book.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "guess", "that", "--", "here", "'s", "what", "I", "thought", "when", "I", "read", "your", "book", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120611pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "RB", ":", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NNPS", "CC", "NNPS", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "WDT", "VBZ", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 157, "question": "How do you actually have a government that works if everyone is an independent?", "question_tokens": ["How", "do", "you", "actually", "have", "a", "government", "that", "works", "if", "everyone", "is", "an", "independent", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "WDT", "VBZ", "IN", "NN", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 158, "answer": "Well, you can still -- you can turn the Democrats and Republicans into special interests, which is what they are anyway.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "you", "can", "still", "--", "you", "can", "turn", "the", "Democrats", "and", "Republicans", "into", "special", "interests", ",", "which", "is", "what", "they", "are", "anyway", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120611pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 166, "question": "These would be independents formerly known as Democrats and Republicans, wouldn't they?", "question_tokens": ["These", "would", "be", "independents", "formerly", "known", "as", "Democrats", "and", "Republicans", ",", "would", "n't", "they", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "MD", "VB", "NNS", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "NNPS", "CC", "NNPS", ",", "MD", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 167, "answer": "No, not necessarily.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "not", "necessarily", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120611pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 173, "question": "You know why?", "question_tokens": ["You", "know", "why", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "WRB", "."], "aSentId": 174, "answer": "Go on.", "answer_tokens": ["Go", "on", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120611pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 175, "question": "You know why?", "question_tokens": ["You", "know", "why", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "WRB", "."], "aSentId": 176, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120611pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 203, "question": "When you hear the president and Republican nominee going at it like this, given the state of economy, what's your reaction?", "question_tokens": ["When", "you", "hear", "the", "president", "and", "Republican", "nominee", "going", "at", "it", "like", "this", ",", "given", "the", "state", "of", "economy", ",", "what", "'s", "your", "reaction", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "CC", "NNP", "NN", "VBG", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "DT", ",", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", ",", "WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 204, "answer": "Well, my reaction, it doesn't matter.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "my", "reaction", ",", "it", "does", "n't", "matter", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120611pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 241, "question": "What do you think?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "think", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 242, "answer": "I think it's awful.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "it", "'s", "awful", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120611pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "VBG", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 262, "question": "So presumably you'll be boycotting FOX and MSNBC on your book tour, will you, Jesse?", "question_tokens": ["So", "presumably", "you", "'ll", "be", "boycotting", "FOX", "and", "MSNBC", "on", "your", "book", "tour", ",", "will", "you", ",", "Jesse", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "RB", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBG", "NNP", "CC", "NNP", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", ",", "MD", "PRP", ",", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 263, "answer": "I won't be boycotting them.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "wo", "n't", "be", "boycotting", "them", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Jesse"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120611pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": [":", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 269, "question": "Really?", "question_tokens": ["Really", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 270, "answer": "-- will have me on.", "answer_tokens": ["--", "will", "have", "me", "on", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120611pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "PRP", "RP", "."], "qSentId": 328, "question": "He has?", "question_tokens": ["He", "has", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "."], "aSentId": 329, "answer": "Well, he is pulling them out.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "he", "is", "pulling", "them", "out", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120611pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 331, "question": "He's pulling them out, isn't he?", "question_tokens": ["He", "'s", "pulling", "them", "out", ",", "is", "n't", "he", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "PRP", "RP", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 332, "answer": "Well, I guess he is.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "guess", "he", "is", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120611pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 346, "question": "What would you do with Iran?", "question_tokens": ["What", "would", "you", "do", "with", "Iran", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 347, "answer": "Well, I'll give you a scenario.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "'ll", "give", "you", "a", "scenario", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Iran"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120611pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", ":"], "qSentId": 370, "question": "So the U.S. -- the U.S. is definitely threatened by these countries in what way?", "question_tokens": ["So", "the", "U.S.", "--", "the", "U.S.", "is", "definitely", "threatened", "by", "these", "countries", "in", "what", "way", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "NNP", ":", "DT", "NNP", "VBZ", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "WP", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 371, "answer": "You don't think --", "answer_tokens": ["You", "do", "n't", "think", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["U.S.", "U.S."]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120611pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "POS", "WP", ":", "DT", "NN", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 435, "question": "What did you make of that?", "question_tokens": ["What", "did", "you", "make", "of", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 436, "answer": "Well, I think that's what -- the defense basically filed that motion today.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "think", "that", "'s", "what", "--", "the", "defense", "basically", "filed", "that", "motion", "today", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120611pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 448, "question": "Is it damaged at all by the fact that quite a few of the boys who are now men obviously have also filed civil complaints, so there is a potential financial incentive here?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "it", "damaged", "at", "all", "by", "the", "fact", "that", "quite", "a", "few", "of", "the", "boys", "who", "are", "now", "men", "obviously", "have", "also", "filed", "civil", "complaints", ",", "so", "there", "is", "a", "potential", "financial", "incentive", "here", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "RB", "DT", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "WP", "VBP", "RB", "NNS", "RB", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "NN", "NNS", ",", "RB", "RB", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "NN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 449, "answer": "I don't think it's damaged.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "think", "it", "'s", "damaged", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Jason Carroll"]}, "docId": "120611pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "WRB", "NNP", "NNP", "VBD", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBG", "PRP$", "NN", "RB", "EX", "."], "qSentId": 455, "question": "Don't they have some right to some recompense to help them deal with the abuse as they go forward?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "n't", "they", "have", "some", "right", "to", "some", "recompense", "to", "help", "them", "deal", "with", "the", "abuse", "as", "they", "go", "forward", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "TO", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 456, "answer": "I saw when Jason Carroll was talking about the defense strategy, you shaking your head vigorously there.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "saw", "when", "Jason", "Carroll", "was", "talking", "about", "the", "defense", "strategy", ",", "you", "shaking", "your", "head", "vigorously", "there", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120611pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "WP", "DT", "NN", "NN", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 457, "question": "You clearly don't make a lot of that, right?", "question_tokens": ["You", "clearly", "do", "n't", "make", "a", "lot", "of", "that", ",", "right", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 458, "answer": "I don't understand what the defense strategy is.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "understand", "what", "the", "defense", "strategy", "is", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120611pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 477, "question": "It is classic grooming behaviors, isn't it, we're looking at?", "question_tokens": ["It", "is", "classic", "grooming", "behaviors", ",", "is", "n't", "it", ",", "we", "'re", "looking", "at", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "NN", "NNS", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 478, "answer": "Oh, absolutely.", "answer_tokens": ["Oh", ",", "absolutely", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120611pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NNS", "RB", "VBP", "DT", "VBZ", "VBG", "TO", "NN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 504, "question": "What's that all about?", "question_tokens": ["What", "'s", "that", "all", "about", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "IN", "DT", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 505, "answer": "I think both sides probably think this is going to advantage them.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "both", "sides", "probably", "think", "this", "is", "going", "to", "advantage", "them", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120611pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "RB", "IN", "DT", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", ",", "IN", "NN", "TO", "DT", "NN", "PRP$", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 545, "question": "Why are you running?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "are", "you", "running", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 546, "answer": "Well, I've been in public service just about all of my adult life, in addition to the time my wife and I spent running a small business.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "'ve", "been", "in", "public", "service", "just", "about", "all", "of", "my", "adult", "life", ",", "in", "addition", "to", "the", "time", "my", "wife", "and", "I", "spent", "running", "a", "small", "business", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120611pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "POS", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 555, "question": "What do you say to those who say, you know, you're no spring chicken and the young guy should get a run?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "say", "to", "those", "who", "say", ",", "you", "know", ",", "you", "'re", "no", "spring", "chicken", "and", "the", "young", "guy", "should", "get", "a", "run", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "DT", "WP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "VBN", "CC", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 556, "answer": "Well, that's a good question.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "that", "'s", "a", "good", "question", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120611pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "EX", "."], "qSentId": 568, "question": "What did you think when you heard that?", "question_tokens": ["What", "did", "you", "think", "when", "you", "heard", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 569, "answer": "Well, I think he's got a good message there.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "think", "he", "'s", "got", "a", "good", "message", "there", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Arizona"]}, "docId": "120611pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "POS", "DT", "NN", "PRP$", "NN", "VBZ", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "RB", "IN", "WP", "POS", "RB", "JJ", "TO", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 575, "question": "Is that true?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "that", "true", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 576, "answer": "I think that's the distraction my opponent has tried to use to move us away from what's really important to the people of Arizona.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "that", "'s", "the", "distraction", "my", "opponent", "has", "tried", "to", "use", "to", "move", "us", "away", "from", "what", "'s", "really", "important", "to", "the", "people", "of", "Arizona", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["November"]}, "docId": "120611pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "WRB", "PRP", "VBZ", "TO", "DT", "NNP", "NN", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 585, "question": "Just for the purposes of clarification, are you a big supporter of the president?", "question_tokens": ["Just", "for", "the", "purposes", "of", "clarification", ",", "are", "you", "a", "big", "supporter", "of", "the", "president", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "NN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 586, "answer": "Well, when it comes to the November election, I will support the president.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "when", "it", "comes", "to", "the", "November", "election", ",", "I", "will", "support", "the", "president", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}]